<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>1. Architectures on Heterogeneous Computing</title>
    <link>http://example.org/unit1/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 1. Architectures on Heterogeneous Computing</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/unit1/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter I</title>
      <link>http://example.org/unit1/cpu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/unit1/cpu/</guid>
      <description>Emma Woodhouse, handsome, clever, and rich, with a comfortable home and happy disposition, seemed to unite some of the best blessings of existence; and had lived nearly twenty-one years in the world with very little to distress or vex her.
She was the youngest of the two daughters of a most affectionate, indulgent father; and had, in consequence of her sister&amp;rsquo;s marriage, been mistress of his house from a very early period.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter II</title>
      <link>http://example.org/unit1/chapter2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/unit1/chapter2/</guid>
      <description>Mr. Weston was a native of Highbury, and born of a respectable family, which for the last two or three generations had been rising into gentility and property. He had received a good education, but, on succeeding early in life to a small independence, had become indisposed for any of the more homely pursuits in which his brothers were engaged, and had satisfied an active, cheerful mind and social temper by entering into the militia of his county, then embodied.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter III</title>
      <link>http://example.org/unit1/chapter3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/unit1/chapter3/</guid>
      <description>Mr. Woodhouse was fond of society in his own way. He liked very much to have his friends come and see him; and from various united causes, from his long residence at Hartfield, and his good nature, from his fortune, his house, and his daughter, he could command the visits of his own little circle, in a great measure, as he liked. He had not much intercourse with any families beyond that circle; his horror of late hours, and large dinner-parties, made him unfit for any acquaintance but such as would visit him on his own terms.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
